although i'm 55 years old i got carded
the other day and it felt great
of course it was at a vaccination
station but i'll take it
they say 55 is a great age i sure hope
so because that's the age i'm going to
be for the next 10 years
55 is a great age because i don't have
to dress to impress anymore because at
55 people are just impressed you're
dressed
when you're a 25 year old man people are
like
that tie doesn't match that shirt that
belt doesn't match those shoes but when
you're a 55 year old man people are like
oh your body's covered that'll do
let's get some wings
the great thing about being 55 is i
don't have to look great i just have to
look great for
55. and living alone with no dependents
took care of that
i went to my 20-year high school reunion
and saw a 38 year old classmate of mine
who's a hard-working dad with six kids i
mistook him for his father
i was like hi mr jackson how's craig
he's like i am craig you idiot
i'm like oh i'm sorry craig i got
confused seeing you here with your
mother he said that's my wife you idiot
i'm like wow how's that brady bunch
thing working out for you
they say that it's harder to stay fit
when you're 55 i think it's easier all
you have to do is adjust your fitness
goals
[Applause]
when i was 25 i went to the gym to get
buff and ripped
now i go to the gym to feel less guilty
about eating pie
as soon as my fitbit says 500 calories
it's goodbye walking track and hello
bakery
25 year old me wanted to be buff 55 year
old me just wants to be regular
year old me was like i just benched 200
with no spotter 55 romeo's like i just
went number two with no spotter
and health club locker room talks a
little bit different between younger men
and older men younger men are like hey
bro
which you take whey protein or wheat
reproaching bro whey protein bro cause
it's way better bro that's why they call
it whey protein bro
but middle aged men are like how do you
get your fiber from powder or chewables
are you kidding i'm 60. i stick
firecrackers up my butt
i was so into bodybuilding at 25 that i
was afraid to appear weak so i wouldn't
let anybody spot me on the bench press
no thanks dude it's only 225 if i can't
get 225 up on my own i deserve a crush
trachea
who knows it might even make my voice
deeper
[Applause]
but at 55 i'll walk up to the biggest
steroid munchers in the gym and go
would you mind clearing the weights off
the bar for me so i don't strain my
forearms
and these guys aren't thinking wow this
dude is weak they're thinking wow this
lady is safety conscious
[Applause]
and although i'm a very youthful 55 the
older i get the harder it is
to relate to younger comedians i work
with not too long ago i worked with a 24
year old comedian and he couldn't
understand why i'm not on tinder
how am i supposed to explain that
somebody half my age how am i supposed
to explain to somebody half my age that
casual romance with a stranger simply
isn't worth downloading another app to
my phone
what's the matter bro don't you like
hooking up with hotties bro i'm like
yeah bro but nava means creating a new
username and password bro
you